http://tinies.com/privacy/#cookie-policy

In-Home Childcare Nursery Recruitment Cr√®ches Event Childcare About Contact
Login
Register
Register as a Childcarer
Register as a Parent
Parent Services Childcare Jobs Nanny Screening Maternity Nannies & Nurses International Training
We have local nanny agencies throughout the UK and Ireland
Job Search Tinies has hundreds of childcare jobs across the UK
Select Job Role
All Jobs --------------------------------- Nanny (all) Mother's Help Nanny Nanny/Housekeeper --------------------------------- Maternity Nanny --------------------------------- Family Buddy --------------------------------- Nursery (all) Area Manager Compliance Officer Deputy Manager Early Years Professn. Head of Room Kitchen Assistant Nursery Administrator Nursery Apprentice Nursery Assistant Nursery Cook Nursery Manager Nursery Nurse NVQ Assessor Operations Director Senior Nursery Nurse --------------------------------- Creche (all) Creche Assistant Creche Dep Manager Creche Manager Creche Supervisor Weekend Assistant Weekend Supervisor --------------------------------- Teaching (all) Course Manager Teacher Teachers Assistant Tutor --------------------------------- Holiday Clubs (all) Holiday Club As. Holiday Club COORD. Hol Club Creche As. Holiday Club Nanny Play Leader / Mng Play Worker Ski Season Nanny Villa Nanny --------------------------------- Social Care (all) Contact Officer Family Support Officer Residential Worker Social Work Assistant
Enter Postcode
1 2 3 5 10 15 20 30 50
Within
miles
Or Select Region
All --------------------------------- London South East (ex London) South West East Midlands West Midlands East of England North West North East Yorkshire Scotland Wales Northern Ireland Republic of Ireland --------------------------------- Overseas
Full Time Permanent
Part Time Temporary
Search
My Short Listed Jobs
These are a few of our favourite thingsParenting tips, ideas on entertaining your children, and much, much more.
Our Favourites
Maternity nurses Support for the first weeks or months of your newborn baby's life.
Maternity
Privacy Notice
Tinies ("Tinies/we") is a recruitment business which provides work-finding services to you, our clients and childcarers ("you")
Tinies must process personal data (including sensitive personal data such as police records or health information) so that we can provide these services to you. Tinies knows that you care how information about you is used, shared and stored, and Tinies assures you that we will do so carefully and sensibly and always in accordance with UK Data Protection laws. You may give your personal details to Tinies directly, such as on an application or registration form, or via our website, or when speaking to a Tinies branch. Or we may collect data from another source such as a jobs board. Under UK law, Tinies must have a legal basis for processing your personal data once collected. For the purposes of providing you with childcare recruitment services or childcare training, we will only use your personal data in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Notice. Tinies has never and will never sell your data to any third party. And we only share your data in accordance with this Privacy Notice and in order to provide our childcare recruitment services to you, or to provide you with childcare training (if you have indicated that you are interested in childcare training). For more information: Tinies Data Protection Policy 1. Collection and use of personal data A. Purpose of processing and legal basis Tinies will collect your personal data (which may include sensitive personal data) and will process your personal data for the purposes of providing you with childcare recruitment services or childcare training. The legal bases we rely upon to offer these services to you are: 1) Consent, where we ask you specific questions about processing your data; 2) Contractual obligation under our terms and conditions, ie we cannot perform the contract with you unless we process your data; and 3) In rare cases, a legal obligation (where we are required to pass on details to a regulatory authority such as Ofsted, DBS or LADO) B. Recipients of data Tinies will process and share your personal data and/or sensitive personal data with the following recipients: 1) Clients of Tinies: for example parents and nurseries who are looking for childcarers. 2) Childcarers of Tinies: if you are a client of Tinies and you are looking for a nanny, then we will have to share details of your job with our childcarers in order to find the best one for you. 3) Our IT company, Sapnagroup: Sapna run our database and organise the storage of our data. Sapna are required to abide by UK Data Protection Laws, and are trusted partners of Tinies. 4) My Family Care Limited ("MFC") the franchisor of Tinies and Bright Horizons Family Solutions Limited (the parent company) and their clients. Tinies is part of MFC and Bright Horizons, and provide emergency nannies to MFC and Bright Horizon clients. 5) Job boards: Tinies uses a number of job boards to advertise jobs and to search for childcarers, such as Reed, Total Jobs, Indeed, CV Library, Gumtree and other local and national job boards. 6) Training companies: if you have told us that you are interested in childcare training courses, then we will process and share your data with our affiliated training companies, including Tinies Training; Broaden HR, The Childcare Company, Flick Learning Ltd, EFAS Ltd and first aid training companies that Tinies uses to help childcarers get trained in Paediatric First Aid. 7) Regulatory Authorities: if we are required to do so, we may have to share your data with Ofsted, DBS, LADO or equivalent. Please also note that Tinies is a franchise business, with a number of Tinies branches operating throughout the UK. Each Tinies branch is a separate legal entity. Tinies branches may share data amongst themselves when carrying out their childcare recruitment services. C. Contractual requirement Your personal data is required to enable us to fulfil our obligations under our Terms and Conditions with you. We cannot offer or provide our childcare recruitment services or childcare training without having to take your data, process it and share it. You are obliged to provide the personal data under the contractual terms with Tinies but if you choose not to provide the data, we cannot perform any childcare requirement services for you, or provide information on childcare training courses. That means we cannot find you a job, for example, or find you a nanny. 2. Overseas If you are a childcarer looking for overseas nanny positions, Tinies may transfer your data to client families who live outside the European Economic Area ('EEA') for the purposes of providing you with overseas work. This would be necessary for the performance of the contract between you and Tinies to find you nanny work where you have specified that you wish to work overseas. 3. Data retention Tinies will retain your personal data only for as long as is necessary, and as detailed below:
Different laws require us to keep different data for different periods of time. For example, if you are a childcarer registered with Tinies, the Conduct of Employment Agencies and Employment Businesses Regulations 2003, require us to keep work-seeker records for at least one year (a) from the date of their creation or (b) after the date on which we last provide you with work-finding services. If you work as a temp for Tinies or are pay-rolled by Tinies, we must also keep your payroll records, holiday pay, sick pay and pensions auto-enrolment records for as long as is legally required by HMRC and associated national minimum wage, social security and tax legislation (all of which we may be required to keep for 3 to 6 years). Other than the timescales listed above, and if you have registered with a Tinies branch, Tinies will retain your data for 6 years from the time when your registration with Tinies is no longer active. This means, for example, if you are a client, your data will be retained for 6 years from when we have found and placed a nanny with you and you no longer require our childcare recruitment services (which means we make your registration with Tinies inactive). Or if you are a childcarer, 6 years from when you have indicated that you are no longer looking for work and your registration with Tinies becomes inactive. 6 years is the time scale within which a client or childcarer of Tinies can bring a contractual claim against Tinies.† We will contact you before the 6 years comes up to check that you are happy for us to delete your data. If you wish us to keep your data for longer, then you can let us know when we contact you. In any case, you have a legal right to ask us to delete your data at any time by contacting Tinies or your local Tinies branch. If there is any safeguarding issue, or safeguarding allegation, we are obliged to keep your data indefinitely. If we are helping you with a training enquiry, or putting you in touch with a training provider, we will only keep your data for as long as it takes for you to complete your training, unless you have indicated that you would like to receive information on future training courses.
4. Your rights Please be aware that you have the following data protection rights:
The right to be informed about the personal data Tinies processes on you; The right of access to the personal data Tinies processes on you; The right to rectification of your personal data; The right to erasure of your personal data in certain circumstances; The right to restrict processing of your personal data; The right to data portability in certain circumstances; The right to object to the processing of your personal data that was based on a public or legitimate interest; The right not to be subjected to automated decision making and profiling; and The right to withdraw consent at any time.
Right to Withdraw Consent: where you have consented to Tinies processing your data you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time by contacting either your Tinies local branch, or by contacting the Tinies Data Protection Officer (see details below) or by emailing info@tinies.com† Right to Erasure of Data: where you wish Tinies to delete your data (subject to certain conditions being met for which see our Data Protection Policy and Procedure), please contact either your Tinies local branch, or the Tinies Data Protection Officer (see details below) or email info@tinies.com. Please note that we are legally obliged to retain certain data even if you make a data deletion request, in accordance with legislation requirements (detailed in paragraph 3 above). 5. Cookie Policy Tinies website uses cookies to store information on your computer. Cookies are small text files located in browser directories. Some of these cookies are essential to make our website work and other cookies help us to improve by giving us some insight into how our website is being used. We use Google Analytics (GA) to track website user interaction. We use this data to determine the number of people using our site, to better understand how they find and use our web pages and to see their journey through the website. Although GA records use data such as your geographical location, device, internet browser and operating system, none of this information personally identifies you to us. GA also records your computer's IP address but Google does not grant us access to this. GA makes use of cookies, details of which can be found on Google's developer guides. We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise trigger across the Internet. AdWords remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the TriggerApp website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. The cookie is used to say "This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page." Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you. We also use the Facebook pixel to determine people who have visited our site and use this for remarketing purposes. Facebook Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you. Disabling cookies on your internet browser will stop GA and Facebook from tracking any part of your visit to pages within this website. We also use PHPSESSID which is used for PHP session maintenance. This allows the client to identify itself to the server and without this the site cannot function. Valid for 1 hour after the cookie is set. 6. Complaints or Enquiries Tinies has appointed a Data Protection Officer (DPO) who is responsible for ensuring Tinies compliance with the Data Protection Laws.† The DPO's contact details are: Name: Global Privacy Officer Email: dataprivacy@brighthorizons.com Tel: 020 3872 9697 If you have a complaint or suggestion or query about Tinies's handling of personal data then please contact the DPO.
How to get in touch Register as a Parent Childcarer Login
Follow us
Find childcareIf you want to hire a nanny in the UK, your local Tinies agency is here to help.
Parent Services
Useful pages
Parent Services Childcare Jobs Mobile Cr√®ches & Events Nursery Staff Recruitment
Read all about it...Our day-to-day life working in childcare and raising a family.
Tinies Blog
Hire a nanny to work abroadTinies International will help to find the ideal British nanny for your family.
Tinies International
A fantastic assessor and mentor from Tinies! She is very knowledgeable, and has supported me, encouraged me, and followed up with me to ensure I was on track to complete the course, which I did much earlier than anticipated.
Dawn, Level 5 Diploma, Childcare Training Courses
Recruitment
Parent Services
Childcare Jobs
Staff Recruitment
Nanny Screening
Maternity Nurses
International
Follow us
Follow and join in the conversation.
Tinies finds and provides the very best childcare across the UK, whatever your needs. It's our whole world
Tinies childcare services include: hire a nanny, find a babysitter, nursery staff supply, mothers' helps, maternity nurses, holiday nannies, mobile cr√®ches, event childcare, on-site childcare,†nanny screening, international nannies, London nanny agencies, nanny payroll service, childcare training courses, nursery management, and emergency childcare. Browse our childcare jobs: nanny jobs, part time nanny jobs, nursery jobs, maternity jobs, cr√®che jobs, overseas nanny jobs, and more!
Aberdeen Banbury Bath Berkshire Birmingham Bradford Brighton Bristol Bromley Buckinghamshire Cambridge Cardiff Cheltenham
Cheshire Cornwall Coventry Croydon Derby Devon Dorset Dundee East Midlands Edinburgh Essex Glasgow Gloucestershire
Hampshire Hampstead Herefordshire Hertfordshire Inverness Ireland Kent Lancashire Leeds Leicester Lincolnshire Liverpool London Nannies (Central)
London Nannies (North) London Nannies (SE) London Nannies (SW) London Nurseries (Central) London Nurseries (North) Manchester Maternity Agency Middlesex Newcastle Norfolk Northampton Northern Ireland Northumberland
Nottingham Overseas Nannies Oxford Portsmouth Reading Republic of Ireland Scotland Central Sheffield Southampton Suffolk Surrey Sussex Swindon
Teesside Tyne & Wear Wales Warwickshire West Midlands Wiltshire Worcestershire Yorkshire
Head Office: Tinies Childcare, 593-599 Fulham Road, London SW6 5UA Tinies is part of My Family Care, owned by Bright Horizons. Registered in England & Wales No: 05905564 We use cookies to provide the best web experience. By visiting this website you are accepting our Privacy and Cookie Policy. Copyright 2020 My Family Care Limited
Mobile CrËches Email a friend and tell them about Tinies!
